<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>go on Christopher Leggett</title>
    <link>https://chrisleggett.me/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in go on Christopher Leggett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 09:42:56 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chrisleggett.me/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grindlists</title>
      <link>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/grindlists/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 09:42:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/grindlists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Grindlists is a web application designed to help gamers organize their grinding
sessions. For any readers who don&amp;rsquo;t know what that means, sometimes a game
requires a player to collect materials to complete a quest or craft an item.
Sometimes those items also require crafting intermediate items, and it can be a
lot to keep track of. The goal of Grindlists is to help gamers keep track of
what items they need, how many they need, and where those items can be found.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang REST API Tip - Use an Embed Parameter to Embed Related Resources</title>
      <link>https://chrisleggett.me/posts/golang-rest-api-embed-parameter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 23:37:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisleggett.me/posts/golang-rest-api-embed-parameter/</guid>
      <description>In a REST API, you often have relations between resources. While you can certainly return IDs for these related objects and require the API consumer to query them, that can be somewhat inconvenient for your users. On the other hand, you certainly don&amp;rsquo;t want to eagerly load these on every request, or you could be sending unnecessarily large payloads in your responses. So what can you do?
In my case, I chose to support a query parameter with the name embed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackernews Clone</title>
      <link>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/hackernews-clone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 21:12:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/hackernews-clone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a small educational project I wrote up to teach myself GraphQL and how to implement a
GraphQL API in Go. It&amp;rsquo;s nothing &lt;strong&gt;too&lt;/strong&gt; fancy, but it might be useful to someone learning GraphQL
themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devmarks</title>
      <link>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/devmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 17:22:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisleggett.me/projects/devmarks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Devmarks is a bookmark manager intended for teams of developers to share
bookmarks to documentation, intranet sites, and other valuable information. It
is still in development so certain aspects of it are subject to change.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
